Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Exhibitions [2016 processing project], 1960-2006; Series 18
  - Gordon Parks: Perspectives, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - GP Family Guides, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Gordon Parks Programs/Calendar, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Parks In Focus: Town Meeting with Gordon Parks, 1997 September 9; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Parks Teacher Workshop, 1997 September 13; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Gordon Parks: An Evening for Educators, 1997 October 21; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Gordon Parks Art & Social Action, 1997 October 25; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - [Gordon Parks], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Gordon Parks: Final Report, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Gordon Parks: Tour/Venues, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Gordon Parks: AAM Design Award, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Gordon Parks; Exhibit Information, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Gordon Parks, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Gordon Parks: Town Meeting, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Gordon Parks: Community Project, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - [Opening Doors], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 22)
  - Town Meeting: Faculty, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 23)
  - Gordon Parks Town Meeting/Students, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 24)
  - Gordon Parks Programs/Calendar, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 25)
  - [Gordon Parks Press Kits], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 26)
  - Gordon Parks: Educational Materials, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 27)
  - [Gordon Parks Teacher Packets], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 28)
  - Gordon Parks: Bibliographies, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 29)
  - Gordon Parks: Acoustiguide, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 30)
  - [Gordon Parks Acoustiguide Sign], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 38, Folder 31)
  - [Raised By Wolves], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - RBW: Final Reports, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - [Raised By Wolves], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - [Raised By Wolves], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Raised by Wolves, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - [Raised By Wolves], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - RBW: Schools, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - RBW: Follow Up (Reviews, Etc), Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Raised by Wolves: Evaluation, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - [Raised By Wolves], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Raised by Wolves: Education Component (Freddie Mac), Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - RBW: Programs, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Raised by Wolves: Performance, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Raised by Wolves: Lectures/Symposia, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - RBW: Teacher Workshop, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Raised by Wolves Educator Workshop, 1995 September 16; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Raised by Wolves; Film/Video, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Raised by Wolves: Jim Goldberg-Checklist/Bios, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Jim Goldberg: Raised by Wolves, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - RBW: List, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - RBW: Community Organizations, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Mental Health Services, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Sasha Bruce, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 23)
  - Operation Runaway, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 24)
  - National Law Center, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 25)
  - [National Runaway Switchboard], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 26)
  - RBW: Student Guide, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 27)
  - RBW: Brochure, Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 28)
  - RBW: Facts, Statistics, Etc., Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 29)
  - [Raised By Wolves Oversized], Circa 1994-1996; Series 18 (Box 39, Folder 30)
  - [Slides], Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 1, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 2, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 3, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 4, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 5, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 6, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 7, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 8, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 9, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 10, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 11, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 12, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 13, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 14, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 15, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Corcoran Cathy VHS 16, Circa 1990; Series 18 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Hospice: Exhibition Meetings, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Hospice: A Photographic Inquiry, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Hospice: Programs, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Public Programs, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Teachers Workshop - Contacts Audience, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Background Material Meetings, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Hospice: Sympoium "A Good Dying", Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Hospice: Workbook for Families, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Hospice: Resources, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Hospice, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Hospice: Regional Listings, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Hospice: List/Invitations, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Hospice: Schedule, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Hospice: Brochure, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Hospice: Bibliography, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Hospice: Venues, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Hospice: Budget, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Hospice: Facts, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - [Loose Hospice], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Hospice: Community Outreach, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - [Hospice Loose], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Hospice: Artists, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 23)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 24)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 25)
  - Hospice: Community Relations, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 26)
  - Hospice, Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 27)
  - [Loose Resource Packs], Circa 1996; Series 18 (Box 41, Folder 28)
  - [Norman Rockwell Slides], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Other Education Materials, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - [Gordon Parks Ed. Files], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Programs/Events, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Expenses, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Acoustiguides & Tours, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Exhibitin Schedules Etc., Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Gordon Parks Bio. Stuff, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Educators' Packets, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Originals, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - [Loose Photos], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - [Loose Photos], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - [Photos], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Misc. Support Development, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - To Mailing List, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - TRS Phase #2, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - TRS Phase #2, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - [Loose ArtReach], Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Marie Moll, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Goldstein, Jan, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Jamora Ilasat, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Job Description, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Development, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Summer Institute, 2001; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - VACOP Visual Arts Community Outreach Program, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - VACOP, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - VACOP, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Camp- Art & Writing Institute, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - VACOP Strategic Planning Notebook, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - VACOP Manual Original, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Corcoran Outreach: Budget/Expenses, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - ArtReach: Payroll, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - ArtReach 2001-2002, Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - ArtReach 2002-2003, Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - [Loose ArtReach], Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - [Loose ArtReach], Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - ECC Summer 2002, Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - ArtReach 2003-2004, Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - [Loose ArtReach], Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Expressions, 2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Expressions, 2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Poetry, Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - [Loose ArtReach], Circa 2001-2004; Series 18 (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Norman Rockwell Info, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - 4 Freedoms: Speech & Essays, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - 4 Freedoms: Research Info., Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - 4 Freedoms: Loose Info., Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Norman Rockwell, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Visitor Circulation (Lord's Report), Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - 4 Freedoms: Flow, Signage, Etc., Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - 4 Freedoms: Press, Etc., Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - 4 Freedoms: Docents / Wkend. Advance, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - 4 Freedoms: Education Programs, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - WWII Memorial & Celebration, 2003-2004; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - 4 Freedoms: Curric. Guide, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - 4 Freedoms: Checklist, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - 4 Freedoms: Wall Text / Labels, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Rockwell Loose Info., Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Thank You Book, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Norman Rockwell's Four Freedoms Book, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Norman Rockwell's Four Freedoms a curriculum for educators images (11 copies), Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Public Attendance, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Four Freedoms: Pamphlet's & Slides, Circa 2002; Series 18 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - CGA African-American Art Educator's Pack, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Rhapsodies in Black: Art of the Harlem Renaissance Info. Pack, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - In Response to Place: Photographs from the Nature Conservancy's Last Great Places CGA Resource Materials, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Leisure & Labor Slides, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Common Ground: Discovering Community in 150 Years of Art, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Hospice: Education Materials, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Facingn Death Images, Insights, and Intervention Book, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Photo Album, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Final Report Community Relations / Outreach Program, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Hospice: A Photographic Inquiry, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Hospice: Education Materials, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Hospice: Educ. Workshop, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Hospice: Book, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Hospice Public Affairs, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Learning Design Associates Inc., Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Hospice Loose Papers, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - [Antiquities to Impressionism Book], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - [Antiquities ot Impressionism from Binder], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Ewald: LTP Workshop, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - [Teacher Magazine, Ewald CV, Loose Correspondence], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Wendy Ewald, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Borad: Brochure/Wall Text/Audio Script, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - The Broad Collections, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - [Loose Clark Collection Documents], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Clark Collection/75th Anniversary, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Clark: Wall Text & Labels, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - [Art Forum Luncheon], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - [Development], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - [Development], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - [Development], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Prop & Dreams, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Painted Sketch, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Roy DeCarava, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 17)
  - Rockwell, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 18)
  - 45th Biennial The Corcoran Collections, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 19)
  - "New World from Old", Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 20)
  - NWFO: Children's Activities, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 21)
  - Suleyman the Magnif at National Gallery of Art, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 22)
  - Banneker '97, 1997; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 23)
  - [Educational Programs other Museum], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 24)
  - Farwell to Bosnia Education Department File, Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 46, Folder 25)
  - [Peale Images from Philadelphia Museum of Art], Circa 1996-1998; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - The Peale Family Legacy, 1997; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - [Loose Peale], 1997; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - ULAE, 1995; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - ULAE Educator Workshop, 1997; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - [ULAE], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Lorna Simpson/Carrie Mae Wems/Clarissa Slight, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - From the Collection: Recent Acquisitions of Photography, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - JS Sargent: Drawings, 1999; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - [The Icing on the Cake], 2001; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Arthur Tress, 2001; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - [Peale Slides], Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Jack Boul, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Petah Coyne, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - 43rd Biennial, 1993; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - [43rd Biennial], 1993; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Richard Bolton, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Cadavre Exquis, 1994; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - [Loose Faberge], 1996; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Faberge: Brochures, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - William Dunlap, 1995-1996; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Family Lives, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Vaclav Havel: A World About Words, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Lois Mailou Jones, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Niek Kemps, 1995; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - American Politicians, 1995; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - David Mordini, 1996; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - The Pervasiveness of Memory, 1995; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Photography & Beyond in Japan, 1995; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Polke: Photoworks, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Project Descriptions RBW, Circa 1993-2006; Series 18 (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Pictures, Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - [Loose Photos], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - TRS Summer Institute, Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Howard County Schools, Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - [School/Museum Information], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Corcoran Gallery Education Department., Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - [Slides (1 of 4)], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - [Slides (2 of 4)], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - [Slides (3 of 4)], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - [Slides (4 of 4)], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - [Loose Photos], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Docent Training Field Trip to the New Arts Foundry (Photo Album), 1997 June; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Party 1994 (Photo Album), Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - [Polaroid Headshots Photo Album], Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - [Photos from African American Teachers Insitute Box], 1999; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Summer Institute for Educators African American Art at the Corcoran (Tape), Circa 1982-2006; Series 18 (Box 49, Folder data_value_missing_fce4bfd9c654ed3968b2ea89103d0fd9)
  - Norrell: Checklist, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Norrell: Artists, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Docents on Common Ground, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - [Norrell Family Day Proposal], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Julia J. Norrell/Collection, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Figuratively Speaking, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Eakins & Swimming Picture, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Lila Wallace/Reader's Digest, 1996-1997; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Manuel Neri, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Bill Newman, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Larry Rivers, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - [Recent Acquisitions], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Ida Applebroog, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Gilded Cage, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Jacob Kainen (90th Birthday Tribute), Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - [Loose Documents], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Renee Keme-Rotan, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - [Facing History], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Douglas, Aaron, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Educators Evening (Bourgeois & Jones), 1994 October 13; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - [Loose], Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Alchemy/Lyle Harris, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - David Driskell Lecture & Booksigning, Circa 1990-1994; Series 18 (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - [Loose Slides], Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - [Slides], Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - [Slides], Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Thurlow Tibbs Memorial, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Harlem Renaissance (To Be Sorted), Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - [Loose Slides], Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Tibbs Lists, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - African American Art Lists, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Black is a Color: Travel Exhibition, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Black is a Color: Travel - Wall Text & Checklist), Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - The Links: Art Reach PAAP, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Links, Alphas, Deltas, Jack & Jill, 100 Concert, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Thurlow Evans Tibbs, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Evans-Tibbs: Works on Paper (Exhibition 1997), Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Evans-Tibbs: "Salon" Gifts, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - [Loose Tibbs], Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Thurlow Evans Tibbs Collection, Circa 1990-1999; Series 18 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - To Conserve a Legacy - HBCU Alumni Weekend, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - To Conserve a Legacy, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Press - To Conserve a Legacy, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Pasat Exhibition Report, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Slides - To Conserve a Legacy, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Checklists/Labels - To Conserve a Legacy, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - To Conserve a Legacy: KPMG Poster Contest, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - To Conserve a Legacy - Historically Black Colleges & University, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - To Conserve a Legacy, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - [Loose - To Conserve a Legacy], Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - [To Conserve a Legacy - Education Packet], Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - [To Conserve a Legacy], Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - [To Conserve a Legacy - Packet], Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Education Materials, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - White House Initiative on HBSCUS, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Printed Materials, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - [To Conserve a Legacy - Catalog], Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Harlem Renaissance: Do Now!, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Harlem Renaissance: Programs, Circa 1999-2000; Series 18 (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - African American Works of Art at the Corcoran, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Harlem Renaissance Tapes 1,2,3, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Harlem Renaissance Tapes 4,5,6,8,9, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Artist Descriptions, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Bourgeois and Jones Slides, Undated; Series 18 (Box 56, Folder 5)